Curriculum Vitae

Mr. Morgan Wilson-Slider Telephone: +44 (0)7759 782850

Email: mwilsonslider1234@outlook.com

An enthusiastic and dedicated individual who has a mature and responsible approach to situations, as a calm and professional person. I have great communication skills that enables me to work within a team environment, but I am also confident in working individually and remotely. I have experience with vast aspects of the developmental process, this is through 5+ years of experience. I have learned a great deal with at designing, creating, and testing web-based applications.

Key Skills

- Leadership, Management, Researching, Reporting, Quality Assurance.
- Project Management (Agile and Waterfall)
- Database Administration (MySQL, Apache)
- Windows and Linux
- Object Oriented Programming (Test Driven Development)
- Networking (Switches, Routing Protocols, LAN & WAN, VPN, Network Packet Analysis, Network Design, IP(TCP / IP / DNS / DHCP)).
- Network Security (Stateful Firewalls, Juniper Firewalls, Cryptography, SAML).
- General Security (Virus and Malware, OAuth)
- Coding Languages (JavaScript, JQuery, CSS, C#, Ajax, SQL, Git, React.js, Node-JS, Playwright, .NET)

Career Summary

2022 - Present: We Heart Digital (Technical Assistant).

Key responsibilities: Support Tickets, Investigating issues on web-based applications and providing solutions. Quality Assurance, a vigorous user test to ensure that all work from myself and others is of the highest quality. Web-Development, using SelectCommerce and WordPress to build and maintain websites for eCommerce clients. Administration, everything from simple documentation for in-house use, to research for acquisitions and Client base research as well as reports and user manuals.

2021 - 2022: Curry's PC World (Sales Adviser).

Key responsibilities: Help customers select products that suit them and offer IT support where necessary. The main aim of working at Curry's PC World was to gain work experience, and to gain some knowledge on hardware, connectivity and to gain a hands-on experience with customer service.

Education

Batcheler's of Science (Hons) Computer and Information Security.

A-Levels – Information Computing Technology, Applied Science, Sociology.

GCSEs - Mathematics, English Language, English Literature, Science, Psychology, Food Technology, Resistant Materials, Information Computing Technology.

2017 - 2021: University of Plymouth. BSc (Hons) Computer and Information Security.

Key Knowledge: Practice coding for various projects both undertaken as individual and group work, while maintaining and following the legal system and ethical guidelines. Through providing documentation to show how the law had been upheld.

Volunteer, Full Stack Developer

November 2022 - Present

Building an interactive website using JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, and CSS for an international event organizer with the purpose of providing an immersive experience for clients to keep track of data and allowing clients to engage with each other.

Personal Interests

International Community Event Coordinator. I host a weekly function where people from around the world get together and participate in an immersive and collaborative storytelling event where creativity can be celebrated and used to overcome obstacles. There are regulars that attend and some people drop in on occasion. Through this I have enhanced my skills in; Strategic Thinking, Creativity, Teamwork, Communication, Problem Solving, Leadership, Flexibility, Facilitation, Commitment, Diversity, Planning, Writing, Storytelling and Teaching as well as Mathematics, Technical Problem Solving, Design, Management, and Probability planning.

Learning and Developing: In my spare time I am currently working on a web application, as well as learning (through Shopify Academy and Analytics Academy) how to use Shopify and Google Analytics. I have recently attended an event: AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals.

References available upon request.